OWEN SENOWITZ

Software Developer

PROFILE

Seeking a Software Development position to utilize my skills as a developer. I've been developing applications and working with databases since 2014 using languages such as C++, Java, Python, C#, JavaScript, and SQL. I've applied those languages to building API's, web front ends and relational databases.

EXPERIENCE

East Carolina University, Assistant Software Developer

SEPT 2021 - PRESENT

Work on developing applications using C# and JavaScript. We use scrum as our agile methodology, with daily standups where we discuss what we did yesterday, what are we doing today and any blockers that we have. This is a part-time assistantship through the college of nursing.

Chick-Fil-A, Team Member

MAY 2018 - JULY 2019

/orked as a frontline cashier taking orders and ringing up ustomers on our POS systems. Worked in the kitchen reparing customers' food and led in training of new mployees.

Arma 3 Altis Life Server, Owner

SEPT 2014 - JAN 2016

Wrote SQF code for a community of over 100 concurrent players. Some of the functionality of the SQF activities including jobs, trading, and economy. Worked closely with administrators and moderators to troubleshoot server issues. Used an AWS EC2 instance to host the game server and used AWS MySQL database to host the players game data. I was able to support my AWS environment through donations via the players on my servers.

CONTACT

- **919-632-6259**
- owen.senowitz@gmail.com
- owen-senowitz.com
- github.com/Owen-Senowitz

SKILLS

- JavaScript 1 year
- Java 2 years
- C++ 2 years
- C# 1 year
- Python 1 year
- SQL 4 years
- AWS 3 years

EDUCATION

East Carolina University

AUG 2019 - PRESENT B.S. in Computer Science

Middle Creek High School

AUG 2015 – JUNE 2019 High School Diploma